Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
6047
Kheel Center
109 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into five sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6047: Archives Information File
6047: Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
6047: Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
6047: Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
6047: Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 23, Folder: 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Text of Principles and a Plan of Action, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Howard J. Samuels
    Notes: November 6, 1964
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Placement Services for Personnel in Higher Education, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
  - Item 2: Counseling and Interviewing Adult Students, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: The National Association of Public School Adult Educators
- Box: 23, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Selected Bibliography of Polish Educational Materials, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: Polish Scientific Publishers
  - Item 2: Higher Education in Poland, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Box: 23, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Higher Education in the U.S.S.R., 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Part-Time Education in the USSR, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Moscow in May 1963, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Structure and Decision-Making in Soviet Education, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Significant Aspects of Soviet Education, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Soviet Education: A Bibliography of English-Language Materials, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Box: 23, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Primer of Life Adjustment Education, 1949; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Author: J. Dan Hull
  - Item 2: The Redirection, Reorganization, and Retooling of Secondary Education, 1948; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Author: Connecticut State Department of Education
    Notes: March 1948
  - Item 3: Basic Issues in Secondary Education, 1945; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Author: New York State Education Department
- Box: 23, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: African Education, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Author: South African Institute of Race Relations
  - Item 2: Urban Education: How Can its Deterioration Be Stopped, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Author: Center for Information on America
    Notes: June 1967
- Box: 23, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Columbia Journal of World Business, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Author: Columbia University
    Notes: Spring 1966
- Box: 23, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Progress of Public Education in the United States of America, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Notes: 1961-62
  - Item 2: Progress of Public Education in the United States of America, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Notes: 1963-64
  - Item 3: An Introduction to Career Education, 1975; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Highlighting the Progress of Education, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Author: Office of Education Centennial Information Committee
  - Item 5: Education, Everybody's Business, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Author: Harold Howe
  - Item 6: Progress of Public Education in the United States of America, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Box: 23, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Education in the United States of America, 1951; Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Author: U.S. Office of Education
- Box: 23, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Education '65, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Digest of Educational Statistics, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Box: 23, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report, 1971; Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Author: Robert A. Plane
    Notes: June 25, 1971
- Box: 23, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Use of the Dictionary of Occupational Titles to Estimate Educational Investment, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Sidney A. Fine
    Notes: August 1968
  - Item 2: Problems of Professional Identity: An Examination of Training for Human Resource Development and Educational Planning, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Adam Curle
  - Item 3: The Role of Education in Economic Development, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Paul Fisher
    Notes: July 10, 1963
  - Item 4: Prospects for Education and Employment, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: National Convention of the League of Women Voters
    Notes: September 1964
  - Item 5: A Better Education; A Better Job, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Lucius F. Cervantes
  - Item 6: Raising Low Incomes Through Improved Education, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Committee for Economic Development
    Notes: September 1965
  - Item 7: Assessing Educational Requirements for Skillpower, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Ontario Economic Council
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet on Trends in the Educational Attainment of Women, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor
  - Item 9: Job Corps Innovations: What Educators Can Learn From Our Job Corps Experience, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: University of Oregon
    Notes: September 1966
  - Item 10: Continuing Education for Women: Current Developments, 1974; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Trends in Educational Attainment of Women, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 1965
  - Item 12: Trends in Educational Attainment of Women, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Trends in Educational Attainment of Women, 1969; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Notes: October 1969
  - Item 14: Trends in Educational Attainment of Women, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Notes: April 1968
- Box: 23, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Education in Yugoslavia and the New Reform, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The Development of a Democratic and Modern System of Education in Yugoslavia, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Author: Mitra Mitrovic
    Notes: August 1961
- Box: 23, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: NDEA Language and Area Centers, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: A Survey of Federal Programs in Higher Education, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: State Plans for Improving Statistical Services, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Box: 23, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Frontiers Past Sixty in Hamilton Ohio, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Box: 23, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Final Report on Compulsory Membership in Professional Organizations Among Credentialed California School Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Author: Senate of the State of California
- Box: 23, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Teacher Exchange Opportunities, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: International Educational Exchange, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Box: 23, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Trading Ideas with the World, 1949; Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
    Author: U.S. Advisory Commission on Educational Exchange
    Notes: March 31, 1949
- Box: 23, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Teacher Exchange Opportunities, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Teacher Exchange Opportunities, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Swords into Plowshares, Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
    Author: U.S. International Educational Exchange Service
  - Item 4: 1954 Fiscal Year, Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
    Author: International Educational Exchange Service
    Notes: October 1, 1954
- Box: 23, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Soviet Training Programs for Africa, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Box: 23, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Educational and Cultural Exchange Opportunities, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Department of State
    Notes: June 1961
- Box: 23, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Innovation and Experiment in Education, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Author: The President's Science Advisory Committee
    Notes: March 1964
  - Item 2: Educational Research in Norway, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Research: Trends and Needs in Educating the Gifted, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Conference on Follow-Up Studies in Educational Research, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Author: University of Wisconsin
    Notes: November 18-19, 1965
- Box: 23, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Use of an Objective Method to Determine Engineering Job Families that Will Apply in Several Companies, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Author: David R. Saunders
    Notes: September 1954
  - Item 2: Development of Procedures for Converting Intelligence Test Scores to a Common Scale, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Author: John C. Flanagan & Paul A. Schwarz
    Notes: July 1958
  - Item 3: What You Should Know About Educational Testing, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Author: J. McV. Hunt
    Notes: July 1966
- Box: 23, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Russian Efficiency, Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
    Language: Russian.
- Box: 23, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Labor Efficiency in Good Times and Bad, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)
    Author: American Management Association
- Box: 23, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Investigation of Senatorial Campaign Expenditures and Use of Governmental Funds, 1939; Publication (Box 23, Folder 26)
    Author: U.S. Senate
    Notes: January 3, 1939
- Box: 23, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: 1966 Political and Election Information, Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of the United States
    Notes: April 1966
  - Item 2: Policies of 83 Companies on Election Activities, Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
    Author: Dartnell Corporation
  - Item 3: Organization for Victory; A Blueprint for Winning Elections, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
    Notes: March 1966
- Box: 23, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Occupational Analysis of Computers in Medical Sciences, 1969; Publication (Box 23, Folder 28)
    Notes: June 1969
- Box: 23, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Significant Ratios for Forty-Five Electric Power Companies, 1944; Publication (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Author: Franklin H. Cook
- Box: 23, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Quarterly Bulletin of Electric Energy Statistics for Europe, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 30)
    Author: United Nations
    Language: English; French; Russian.
- Box: 23, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Case for Competition in Electric Power, 1956; Publication (Box 23, Folder 31)
    Author: Clay L. Cochran & Ron Ross
- Box: 23, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Electrical Machinery: I, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
    Author: National Industrial Conference Board
  - Item 2: Electrical Machinery: II, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Box: 23, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Occupations in Electronic Computing Systems, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
    Notes: July 1965
  - Item 2: Electronic Data Processing, 1963; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Report to the President on the Management of Automatic Data Processing in the Federal Government, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of the Budget
    Notes: February 1965
  - Item 4: Date Processing Systems and Employment Expectations: Indianapolis, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
    Author: Research and Statistics
    Notes: January 1964
  - Item 5: Staff Titles and Job Descriptions in Commercial Data Processing, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Technology
  - Item 6: Automatic Data Processing, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
    Author: Department of Scientific Industrial Research
  - Item 7: The Computer, Is Your Company Ready for it?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Box: 23, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Electrical Machinery: I, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Electrical Machinery: II, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Box: 23, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Cases in Data Processing, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
    Author: Intercollegiate Case Clearing House
- Box: 23, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Some Thoughts on the Impact of Computerized Management Information Systems on Corporate Management-Staff Relationships, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 36)
    Author: Robert L. Johnson
    Notes: March 22, 1967
- Box: 23, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Electronic Data Processing and Personnel Management, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
    Author: University of California, Los Angeles
    Notes: July 19, 1965
  - Item 2: The Computer in Personnel Work, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
    Author: Edgar Wille
  - Item 3: ADP in Public Personnel Administration, 1969; Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
    Author: Public Administration Service
- Box: 23, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Annotated Bibliography on Simulation in the Social Sciences, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
    Author: John J. Hartman
- Box: 23, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Elementary and Secondary Education Amendments of 1966, Publication (Box 23, Folder 39)
    Notes: October 3, 1966
- Box: 23, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Outflow of Trained Personnel from Developing Countries, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
    Notes: November 5, 1968
  - Item 2: Scientific Brain Drain from the Developing Countries, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
    Author: Committee on Government Operations
    Notes: March 28, 1968
- Box: 23, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Modernization and the Migration of Talent, 1970; Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
    Author: The Committee on the International Migration of Talent
    Notes: January 1970
  - Item 2: The Interagency Council and the "Brain Drain" in Developing Countries, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
    Notes: October 6, 1967
  - Item 3: International Migration of Talent from and to the Less-Developed Countries, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
    Author: The Ditchley Foundation
    Notes: February 16-19, 1968
  - Item 4: Current Problems of Immigration Policy, Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
    Author: E.P. Hutchinson
  - Item 5: Memorandum on Immigration Policy, Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
    Author: International Labour Office
- Box: 23, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: The New Immigration Law: What's in it? How Much of a Change? Is it an Improvement?, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
    Notes: January 1966
  - Item 2: The Act of October 3, 1965 "To Amend the Immigration and Nationality Act; and for Other Purposes, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
    Author: American Council for Nationalities Service
    Notes: November 30, 1965
  - Item 3: Immigration Procedures and Labor Clearances, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
    Notes: July 11, 1966
- Box: 23, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Right of Way Conference, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 43)
    Author: University of Alabama
- Box: 23, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: How I See My Work, Publication (Box 23, Folder 44)
    Author: Yale University
- Box: 23, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Acceptance and Resistance, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
    Author: Organisation for Economic Co-Operation and Development
  - Item 2: Can Unfavorable Employee Attitudes be Changed?, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
    Author: Bureau of National Affairs
    Notes: December 1961
- Box: 24, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Administering An Employee Opinion Survey, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Box: 24, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: What You Should Know About Employee Attitudes, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The SRA Employee Inventory, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Author: Science Research Associates
- Box: 24, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Trends in Employee Thinking on Simple Economics, 1950; Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Author: Opinion Research Corporation
    Notes: February 1950
  - Item 2: What Employees Say About Management's Leadership, 1954; Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 1954
  - Item 3: What Employees Say About Management's Leadership, 1954; Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Morale and Motivation in Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Author: Daniel Katz
    Notes: February 19, 1949
- Box: 24, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employee Attitudes Surveys, 1965; Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Author: University of Michigan
- Box: 24, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Workers' Attitudes and the Acceptability of Shift-Work in New Zealand Manufacturing Industry, 1969; Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Author: Stephen Griew & Eileen Philipp
  - Item 2: Job Values of Educationally Disadvantaged Students, 1968; Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Author: Julius Rosen
- Box: 24, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefit Schemes, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Author: Industrial Welfare Society
    Notes: July 1949
- Box: 24, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How to Get a Bigger Return From Your Employee Benefit Dollars, 1957; Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Notes: January 1957
  - Item 2: Making Employee Benefit Dollars Work Harder, 1950; Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Notes: May 1950
  - Item 3: Railroad Employees' Benefits, 1952; Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Author: Commodity Research Publications Corp
  - Item 4: The Midwest Survey of Employee Benefit Plans, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Author: Research Council for Economic Security
    Notes: August 1949
- Box: 24, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Social Security in Industry, 1948; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Notes: June 1948
  - Item 2: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: St. Louis, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Notes: January 1949
  - Item 3: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: Pittsburgh, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 1949
  - Item 4: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: Minneapolis, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: St. Paul, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: Salt Lake City, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Notes: September 1949
- Box: 24, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans, Chicago, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: Michigan, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Notes: April 1949
  - Item 3: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: Cleveland, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: Indianapolis, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Survey of Employee Benefit Plans: Houston, 1949; Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Notes: November 1949
- Box: 24, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Additional Employee Health Benefit Plans, 1965; Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Post Office and Civil Service
    Notes: June 8 & August 24, 1965
  - Item 2: Christmas and New Year's Plansin 188 Companies, 1962; Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Box: 24, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits in 1974, Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Author: L.M. Cathles
  - Item 2: Employee Chirstmas Bonus and Gift Practices, 1966; Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Box: 24, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Fringe Benefit Practices, 1969; Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 1969
  - Item 2: Fringe Benefits in the 1970s, 1968; Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Author: University of Arizona
    Notes: May 1968
  - Item 3: Fringes: Benefits or Burdens, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Author: Warren A. Lacke
  - Item 4: Fringe Benefits, 1964; Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Notes: July 1964
  - Item 5: Fringe Benefits, 1967; Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Notes: January 1967
- Box: 24, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employer-Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Author: William M. Mercer Limited
  - Item 2: Pay Allowances and Other Policies Covering Employees Called to Military Service, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Current Comments on Pension and Profit-Sharing Plans, 1962; Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Author: Chemical Bank New York Trust Company
    Notes: Winter 1962
  - Item 4: RIA Pooled Intelligence, 1969; Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Author: Research Institute of America
  - Item 5: Insurance Benefits in Urban Areas - 1961-1962, 1963; Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Notes: May 16, 1963
  - Item 6: Trends in Employee Benefits, 1961; Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Author: Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc.
    Notes: March 31, 1961
- Box: 24, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: What Other Companies Do and What Their Employees Think They Should Do, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
    Author: Greyvan Lines Incorporated
- Box: 24, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Legal and Fringe Benefits in Belgium, 1962; Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
    Author: Federation Des Industries Belges
    Notes: October 1962
- Box: 24, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Fringe Benefits, 1966; Publication (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Author: Princeton University
- Box: 24, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 24, Folder 23)